pcl.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy | PCL

PCL Constructors Inc. (herein “PCL”) is committed to providing a website that respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information that is collected, used, or disclosed while using the PCL website. Personal information means any information that permits an individual to be identified, but does not include your name, title and business contact information, as these are not subject to privacy restrictions. 

The only personal information PCL collects through the PCL website is the information voluntarily supplied by you if you contact PCL through the website. PCL does not use “cookies” to track how visitors may use the PCL site. Information collected through the PCL website is not disclosed to anyone other than PCL employees, consultants, or agents on a “need to know” basis only. 

This website may contain links to other sites and other websites may link to this website. PCL is not responsible for, and has no control over, the content or privacy policies, practices, or actions of the third parties that operate these websites. You should review the privacy policies of those websites before providing them with personal information. 

We caution that internet communications are vulnerable to interception, use, and/or alteration by person(s) other than the intended recipient. While PCL has implemented certain safeguards to reduce this risk, internet transmissions to and from PCL are still vulnerable. If you choose to communicate by the internet, you do so at your sole risk. 

Please refer to the PCL Terms of Use for additional information concerning the terms of use in relation to the PCL website.  

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contract our Privacy Officer at [ABWallace@pcl.com](mailto:ABWallace@pcl.com) or (780) 733-5216. 

By using this website, you are consenting to the contents of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with it, please do not use this website. PCL reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without further notice and PCL encourages you to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly.
